Herman Langinger Music Publishing Files
Music Division, Library of Congress
Guides to Special Collections in the Music Division of the Library of Congress
Herman Langinger Music Publishing Files 1889-1972 (bulk 1927-1955)
ML31.L36
Langinger, Herman
approximately 650 items 12 containers 4.0 linear feet
Music Division Library of Congress Washington, D.C.
Herman Langinger was a music engraver, printer, and editor for New Music Society of California and other influential music publishers. The collection contains pre-publication and published music materials, including annotated manuscript and holograph scores and proof copies, as well as correspondence with composers and publishing associates. It also includes a comprehensive run of published editions from New Music and various editions from other publishers with whom Langinger worked, namely his own Golden West Music Press in Hollywood, Calif., Delkas Music Publishing Company, and Affiliated Musicians, Inc.
Selected Search Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the Library's online catalog. They are grouped by name of person or organization, by subject or location, and by occupation and listed alphabetically therein.
People
Cage, John.; Carter, Elliott, 1908- --Correspondence.; Castelnuovo-Tedesco, Mario, 1895-1968.; Chávez, Carlos, 1899-1978.; Cowell, Henry, 1897-1965--Correspondence.; Cowell, Henry, 1897-1965.; Ives, Charles, 1874-1954.; Langinger, Herman--Correspondence.; Langinger, Herman.; Riegger, Wallingford, 1885-1961--Correspondence.; Ruggles, Carl, 1876-1971.; Schoenberg, Arnold, 1874-1951.; Slonimsky, Nicolas, 1894-1995--Correspondence.; Toch, Ernst, 1887-1964.; Ussachevsky, Vladimir, 1911-1990--Correspondence.; Varèse, Edgard, 1883-1965.; Wigglesworth, Frank, 1918-1996--Correspondence.
Organizations
Affiliated Musicians, Inc.; Delkas Music Publishing Company.; Golden West Music Press.; New Music Society of California.
Subjects
Music printing--United States.; Music publishers--United States.; Music publishing--United States.; Music--Manuscripts.; Music--United States--20th century.
Titles
New music.; New music.
Form/Genre
Correspondence.
Administrative Information
Provenance
Purchase, Music Division, 2011.
Accruals
No further accruals are expected.
Other Repositories
The Music Division of the New York Public Library for the Performing Arts contains the New Music Society papers, circa 1927-1936.
Access and Restrictions
The Herman Langinger Music Publishing Files are open to research. Researchers are advised to contact the Music Division prior to visiting in order to determine whether the desired materials will be available at that time.
Certain restrictions to use or copying of materials may apply.
Biographical Note
Herman Langinger (1908-1979) was born in Spas, Austria. He immigrated to the United States as a teenager and eventually settled in New York City, where he cultivated the craft of music engraving. After working on the score of Charles Ives' Symphony no. 4, Langinger became known for handling difficult contemporary works. In 1928, he moved to San Francisco and started his own publishing house, Golden West Music Press. He subsequently began publishing Henry Cowell's quarterly serial New Music and became an influential figure in West Coast avant-garde circles. Langinger engraved such high profile pieces as Edgar Varese's Ionisation and works by Carl Ruggles, Roy Harris, and Arnold Schoenberg.
After Cowell was imprisoned in 1936, Langinger, along with Gerald Strang, became co-managers of Cowell’s New Music Society, where they worked hard to keep the organization financially solvent. In his later years, Langinger became the owner of Highland Music Press in Los Angeles. He died in 1979.
Scope and Content Note
The Herman Langinger Music Publishing Files contain materials accrued from 1927 to 1955 while Langinger worked as an engraver and publisher at his own Golden West Music Press in Hollywood, Calif. Most of the materials are related to the production of Henry Cowell's quarterly publication New Music. The collection includes holograph manuscript scores, edited score paste-ups, negative and positive proof copies, printed editions of New Music, financial receipts, notes/corrections, and correspondence (often from major composers) relating to publication. Similar materials exist for Langinger's other engraving commitments, notably Delkas Music Publishing Company and Affiliated Musicians, Inc., both in Los Angeles, Calif. The files contain works by many leading 20th century composers, such as John Cage, Charles Ives, Carl Ruggles, Mario Castelnuovo-Tedesco, Ernst Toch, Edgar Varèse, and Arnold Schoenberg. Represented as well are Latin American composers, namely Carlos Chávez (stemming from Cowell's interest in pan-American music) and various European and Soviet composers.
Langinger's collection of holograph manuscript scores, often annotated by the composers, is substantial and spans the entire period that New Music was published. The plate and/or transfer proofs and paste-ups represent the largest components of the files and provide evidence of Langinger's intricate engraving process. Although the published edition file copies of New Music rarely are annotated, they form a comprehensive collection of the quarterly's total production. Correspondence interspersed within the files generally pertains to the music submitted for publication and provides insights as to the working partnership between composer, editor, and publisher. A large percentage of this correspondence is from members of New Music's editorial board, which included notable composers Elliott Carter, Henry Cowell, Wallingford Riegger, Nicolas Slonimsky, Vladimir Ussachevsky, and Frank Wigglesworth. A handful of related publishing materials, mostly shop tickets, rounds out the collection.
Organization of the Herman Langinger Music Publishing Files
The Herman Langinger Music Publishing Files are organized in two series:
Project Files, 1889-1972
Miscellany, 1944-1948
http://lccn.loc.gov/2011570509
Container List
- Project Files, 1889-1972 (Box 1-12)
  Holograph manuscript scores, publisher's plate/transfer proofs, manuscript or printed score paste-ups, notes, correspondence, and published editions of New Music quarterly and other published editions by affiliated firms such as Delkas Music Publishing Company and Affiliated Musicians, Inc. Many scores and proof copies bear annotations and corrections by the composers. Date of composition or publication copyright is provided for each title if known.
  Arranged alphabetically by composer, and by title of composition therein.
  - Achron, Joseph
    - Sextet, op. 73 for flute, oboe, clarinet, bassoon, French horn, and trumpet, 1938
      - Holograph manuscript score paste-up, Incomplete. (Box-folder 1/1)
      - Printed score (Box-folder 1/1)
    - Statuettes (piano), 1930
      - Printed score (Box-folder 1/1)
  - Antheil, George
    - Sonata no. 2: The airplane (piano), 1931
      - Publisher's proof (Box-folder 1/2)
      - Printed score (Box-folder 1/2)
  - Ardévol, José
    - Sonatina (piano), 1934
      - Holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 1/3)
      - Printed score (Box-folder 1/3)
      - Correspondence (Box-folder 1/3)
  - Babbitt, Milton
    - Composition for four instruments (flute, violin, clarinet, cello), 1949
      - Manuscript score paste-up (Box-folder 1/4)
      - Printed score (Box-folder 1/4)
  - Bacon, Ernst
    - Six songs (voice, piano), 1942
      - Publisher's proof (Box-folder 1/5)
      - Printed score (Box-folder 1/5)
      - Correspondence, Includes one letter from Bacon. (Box-folder 1/5)
    - Ten songs (voice, piano), 1928
      - Printed score, Self-published edition by Bacon. (Box-folder 1/6)
  - Barrymore, Lionel
    - Johnny, dear (voice, piano), 1944, Words by Dailey Paskman.
      - Publisher's proof (Box-folder 1/7)
      - Printed score (Box-folder 1/7)
  - Bartók, Béla see also Box 1, Purcell, Henry
    - Four dirges (piano), 1945, New revision by the composer.
      - Publisher's proof (Box-folder 1/8)
      - Printed score (Box-folder 1/8)
  - Becker, John J.
    - Concerto for horn in F and orchestra, 1936
      - Printed score (Box-folder 1/9)
      - Correspondence (Box-folder 1/9)
    - Soundpiece no. 4: second string quartet, 1948
      - Printed score (Box-folder 1/9)
      - Correspondence (Box-folder 1/9)
  - Berger, Arthur
    - Three poems of Yeats (voice, flute, clarinet, cello), 1940, Texts taken from Yeats' Words for music, perhaps.
      - Manuscript score paste-up (Box-folder 1/10)
      - Printed score (Box-folder 1/10)
  - Beyer, Johanna Magdalena
    - IV (percussion ensemble), 1935
      - Holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 10/4)
      - Printed score (Box-folder 10/4)
  - Biggs, Richard Keys
    - American hymn (voice, piano), undated
      - Publisher's proof (Box-folder 1/11)
    - Andantino (organ), 1945
      - Holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 1/11)
      - Publisher's proof (Box-folder 1/11)
      - Printed score (Box-folder 1/11)
  - Bowles, Paul Frederic
    - Cafe sin nombre (piano), 1933
      - Publisher's proof (Box-folder 2/11)
      - Printed score (Box-folder 2/11)
    - Danger de mort: IV (voice, piano), 1934, Text by Georges Linze.
      - Publisher's proof (Box-folder 2/11)
      - Printed score (Box-folder 2/11)
    - Danger de mort: VI (voice, piano), 1934, Text by Georges Linze.
      - Publisher's proof (Box-folder 2/11)
      - Printed score (Box-folder 2/11)
    - Letter to Freddy (voice, piano), 1935, Text by Gertrude Stein.
      - Publisher's proof (Box-folder 2/11)
      - Printed score (Box-folder 2/11)
    - Scènes d'Anabase: III (voice, oboe, piano), 1932, Text by Saint-Jean Perse.
      - Publisher's proof (Box-folder 2/11)
      - Printed score (Box-folder 2/11)
  - Bradley, Will
    - The deep quarry (clarinet choir), 1948
      - Printed score (Box-folder 1/12)
    - Honeysuckle and clover (brass choir), 1948
      - Printed score (Box-folder 1/12)
  - Brooks, Ernest
    - Piano sonata no. 3. Toccata, 1931-1935
      - Photocopied manuscript score (Box-folder 1/13)
      - Publisher's proof (Box-folder 1/13)
      - Printed score (Box-folder 1/13)
      - Correspondence (Box-folder 1/13)
  - Brown, Merton
    - Cantabile for string orchestra, 1946
      - Publisher's proof (Box-folder 1/14)
      - Printed score (Box-folder 1/14)
      - Correspondence (Box-folder 1/14)
    - Cantabile: piano version, 1946
      - Publisher's proof (Box-folder 1/14)
  - Cage, John
    - Amores: for piano and percussion, 1943
      - Printed score (Box-folder 2/1)
      - Correspondence, Two letters from Henry Cowell. (Box-folder 2/1)
      - Notes and corrections (Box-folder 2/1)
  - Carrillo, Julián
    - Preludio a Cristobal Cólon (vocalise with instrumental ensemble), 1934
      - Holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 2/2)
      - Publisher's proof (Box-folder 2/2)
      - Printed score (Box-folder 2/2)
      - Notes (Box-folder 2/2)
  - Carter, Elliott
    - Pastoral for piano and viola, English horn, or clarinet, 1945
      - Printed score and parts (Box-folder 2/3)
      - Correspondence, One letter from Carter. (Box-folder 2/3)
  - Carvajal, Armando
    - Three pieces for children (piano), 1939
      - Publisher's proof (Box-folder 2/4)
      - Printed score (Box-folder 2/4)
      - Correspondence (Box-folder 2/4)
  - Castelnuovo-Tedesco, Mario
    - Fantasy on themes of Donizetti's Daughter of the Regiment. Romance (violin, piano), 1944
      - Publisher's proof (Box-folder 2/5)
      - Printed score (Box-folder 2/5)
  - Cazden, Norman
    - Sonatina (piano), 1940
      - Printed score (Box-folder 2/6)
  - Chávez, Carlos
    - Seven pieces for piano, 1936
      - Printed scores (Box-folder 2/9)
    - Sinfonía no. 5 for string orchestra, 1954
      - Printed score (Box-folder 2/10)
    - Sonata for piano, 1928
      - Photocopied holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 2/7)
      - Publisher's proof (Box-folder 2/7)
      - Printed score (Box-folder 2/7)
    - Sonatina for violin and piano, 1928
      - Printed scores, One score is a 1934 reprint of the first edition. (Box-folder 2/8)
    - Spiral (Espira): movement for violin and piano, 1934
      - Holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 2/11)
      - Publisher's proof (Box-folder 2/11)
      - Printed score (Box-folder 2/11)
  - Cleghorn, James
    - How do you like this?: three ironies for piano, 1938
      - Publisher's proof (Box-folder 5/2)
      - Printed score (Box-folder 5/2)
  - Collins, Anthony
    - The dancing master. Overture (string orchestra), 1946
      - Holograph manuscript score paste-up (Box-folder 2/12)
      - Printed score paste-up (Box-folder 2/12)
      - Printed score (Box-folder 2/12)
  - Copland, Aaron
    - As it fell upon a day: song for soprano with accompaniment for flute and clarinet, 1923, Words by Richard Barnefield.
      - Printed score (Box-folder 2/13)
  - Cowell, Henry
    - Hilarious curtain opener (piano), 1939, Incidental music written for a production of Jean Cocteau's play Les Maries de la tour Eiffel
      - Holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 3/1)
      - Publisher's proof (Box-folder 3/1)
      - Printed score (Box-folder 3/1)
      - Correspondence, Three letters from Cowell. (Box-folder 3/1)
    - Maestoso for piano, 1940
      - Printed score (Box-folder 3/2)
    - Ritournelle (piano), 1939, Incidental music written for a production of Jean Cocteau's play Les Maries de la tour Eiffel
      - Holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 3/1)
      - Publisher's proof (Box-folder 3/1)
      - Printed score (Box-folder 3/1)
      - Correspondence (Box-folder 3/1)
    - Two woofs (piano), 1947
      - Manuscript score paste-up (Box-folder 3/3)
      - Printed score paste-up (Box-folder 3/3)
      - Printed score (Box-folder 3/3)
      - Correspondence (Box-folder 3/3)
  - Crawford, Ruth
    - Four preludes for piano, 1928
      - Printed score (Box-folder 3/4)
    - String quartet, 1931
      - Photocopied manuscript score (Box-folder 3/5)
      - Publisher's proofs (Box-folder 3/5)
      - Printed score (Box-folder 3/5)
      - Correspondence (Box-folder 3/5)
  - Creston, Paul
    - Seven theses: for piano, 1935
      - Holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 3/6)
      - Printed score (Box-folder 3/6)
      - Correspondence (Box-folder 3/6)
    - Suite for E♭ alto saxophone or B♭ clarinet and piano, 1938
      - Printed score (Box-folder 3/6)
      - Correspondence (Box-folder 3/6)
  - Dahl, Ingolf
    - Variations on a Swedish folktune (flute), 1945
      - Printed score (Box-folder 11/7)
  - Davidenko, Alexander Alexandrovich
    - Song of a shepherd perishing in the mountains: no. 3 from Suite for chorus à capella, written on the basis of Chechen folk melodies, 1934
      - Publisher's proof (Box-folder 3/7)
      - Printed score (Box-folder 3/7)
  - Davidson, Harold G.
    - Auto accident (percussion ensemble), 1936
      - Holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 10/4)
      - Printed score (Box-folder 10/4)
  - Diggle, Roland
    - Chiaroscuro: for piano solo, 1947
      - Holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 3/8)
      - Publisher's proofs (Box-folder 3/8)
      - Printed score (Box-folder 3/8)
  - Erdody, Leo
    - I bet you (voice, piano), 1945, Words by Margel Gluck.
      - Holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 3/9)
      - Publisher's proofs (Box-folder 3/9)
      - Printed score (Box-folder 3/9)
  - Feldman, Morton
    - Illusions: for piano, 1950
      - Manuscript score paste-up (Box-folder 3/10)
      - Printed score (Box-folder 3/10)
  - Fernandez, Oscar Lorenzo
    - Batuque: negro dance from the opera Malazarte (orchestra), 1939, Poem by Graca Oranha.
      - Printed score (Box-folder 3/11)
    - Moda (piano), 1942
      - Publisher's proof (Box-folder 11/10)
      - Printed score (Box-folder 11/10)
      - Correspondence, Includes five letters from Henry Cowell. (Box-folder 11/10)
  - Ficher, Jacobo
    - Sonatina for piano, B♭ trumpet and E♭ alto saxophone, op. 21, 1932
      - Holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 4/1)
      - Printed score (Box-folder 4/1)
      - Correspondence (Box-folder 4/1)
  - Fine, Vivian
    - The Great Wall of China (voice, flute), 1947, Text by Franz Kafka.
      - Manuscript score paste-up (Box-folder 4/2)
      - Printed score (Box-folder 4/2)
      - Correspondence (Box-folder 4/2)
  - Finney, Ross Lee
    - Piano sonata in D minor, 1933
      - Printed score (Box-folder 4/3)
  - Franco, Johan
    - Theme and variations for piano, 1944
      - Photocopied holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 4/4)
  - Fuleihan, Anis
    - Sonatina no. 1 (piano), undated
      - Photocopied holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 4/5)
  - García Caturla, Alejandro
    - Preludio corto no. 1 (piano), 1927
      - Holograph manuscript score, In caption: Julio 1927; At bottom of p. [3]: Remedios, Cuba, Enero 19/1928 (Box-folder 1/3)
      - Printed score (Box-folder 1/3)
      - Correspondence (Box-folder 1/3)
    - Sonata corta (piano), 1927
      - Printed score (Box-folder 1/3)
  - Gideon, Miriam
    - Canzona for piano solo, 1945
      - Photocopied holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 4/6)
      - Printed score paste-up (Box-folder 4/6)
      - Printed score (Box-folder 4/6)
  - Gnattali, Radames
    - Chôro (piano), 1942
      - Publisher's proof (Box-folder 11/10)
      - Printed score (Box-folder 11/10)
      - Correspondence, Includes five letters from Henry Cowell. (Box-folder 11/10)
  - Goldman, Richard Franko
    - Hymn for brass choir, 1939
      - Printed score (Box-folder 6/5)
  - Grechaninov, Aleksandr Tikhonovich
    - O God, forgive Thou me: for mixed voices, a cappella, 1953
      - Printed score paste-up (Box-folder 4/9)
      - Printed score (Box-folder 4/9)
  - Green, Ray
    - Four short songs, no. 2: Fog (voice, piano), 1934, Text by Carl Sandburg.
      - Publisher's proof (Box-folder 4/7)
      - Printed score (Box-folder 4/7)
      - Correspondence (Box-folder 4/7)
    - Four short songs, no. 4: Summer grass (voice, piano), 1934, Text by Carl Sandburg.
      - Publisher's proof (Box-folder 4/7)
      - Printed score (Box-folder 4/7)
      - Correspondence (Box-folder 4/7)
    - Jig for a concert (2 pianos), 1953
      - Printed scores (Box-folder 4/8)
    - Sonatina for piano, 1934
      - Publisher's proof (Box-folder 4/7)
      - Printed score (Box-folder 4/7)
      - Correspondence (Box-folder 4/7)
    - Three inventories of Casey Jones (percussion ensemble), 1936
      - Holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 10/4)
      - Printed score (Box-folder 10/4)
    - Two madrigals: Hey nonny no; Sea charm (voices), 1934
      - Publisher's proof (Box-folder 4/7)
      - Printed score (Box-folder 4/7)
      - Correspondence (Box-folder 4/7)
  - Gudauskas, Giedra
    - Norėčiau skristi... (voice), 1972
      - Printed score (Box-folder 4/10)
  - Guarnieri, Camargo
    - Valsa (piano), 1942
      - Publisher's proof (Box-folder 11/10)
      - Printed score (Box-folder 11/10)
      - Correspondence, Includes five letters from Henry Cowell. (Box-folder 11/10)
  - Haines, Edmund
    - Slow dance: for organ, 1948
      - Printed score (Box-folder 1/12)
  - Hajos, Karl
    - This simple song (voice, piano), 1942, Words by Leo Erdody.
      - Photocopied holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 4/11)
      - Publisher's proofs (Box-folder 4/11)
      - Printed score (Box-folder 4/11)
  - Hall, Ariel
    - Overtones (voice, harp or piano), 1944, Poem by William Alexander Percy.
      - Photocopied holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 4/12)
      - Publisher's proofs (Box-folder 4/12)
  - Harris, Roy
    - Trio for pianoforte, violin, and violoncello, 1936
      - Printed score (Box-folder 4/13)
      - Holograph manuscript notes about third movement (Box-folder 4/13)
  - Harris, William see Box 4, Verdi, Giuseppe see Box 4, Wagner, Richard
  - Harrison, Lou
    - Alleluia for orchestra, 1948
      - Printed score (Box-folder 5/1)
    - Prelude for grand piano, 1937
      - Publisher's proof (Box-folder 5/2)
      - Printed score (Box-folder 5/2)
      - Correspondence (Box-folder 5/2)
    - Saraband (piano), 1937
      - Publisher's proof (Box-folder 5/2)
      - Printed score (Box-folder 5/2)
      - Correspondence (Box-folder 5/2)
    - Six sonatas for cembalo or pianoforte, 1943
      - Holograph manuscript score paste-up (Box-folder 5/1)
      - Printed score (Box-folder 5/1)
      - Correspondence, One letter from Henry Cowell. (Box-folder 5/1)
  - Hassan, Al
    - I'm walkin' out (voice, unspecified instruments), undated
      - Photocopied holograph manuscript lead sheet (Box-folder 5/3)
    - Should pretending end (voice, unspecified instruments), undated
      - Photocopied holograph manuscript lead sheet (Box-folder 5/3)
    - (Sometimes we're feeling) Sometimes small (voice, unspecified instruments), undated
      - Photocopied holograph manuscript lead sheet (Box-folder 5/3)
  - Heilner, Irwin
    - Second rhapsody: for tenor and piano four hands, 1935, Words by William Carlos Williams.
      - Holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 6/11)
      - Printed score (Box-folder 6/11)
  - Heller, James G.
    - Three songs for soprano, 1953, Texts taken from Robert Nathan's The green leaf.
      - Printed score (Box-folder 5/4)
  - Herrmann, Bernard
    - Sinfonietta: for string orchestra, 1936
      - Publisher's proof (Box-folder 5/5)
      - Holograph manuscript corrections (Box-folder 5/5)
      - Printed score (Box-folder 5/5)
  - Hovhaness, Alan
    - Mihr: for two pianos, 1945
      - Printed score (Box-folder 5/6)
  - Humphrey, Doris
    - Dance rhythms (percussion ensemble), 1936, Notated by Wallingford Riegger.
      - Holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 10/4)
      - Printed score (Box-folder 10/4)
      - Notes (Box-folder 10/4)
  - Ives, Charles
    - 22 (piano), 1912
      - Manuscript score paste-up (Box-folder 3/3)
      - Printed score paste-up (Box-folder 3/3)
      - Printed score (Box-folder 3/3)
      - Correspondence (Box-folder 3/3)
    - Eighteen songs (voice, piano), 1894-1923, Texts by several authors.
      - Publisher's proof (Box-folder 5/8)
      - Printed score (Box-folder 5/8)
      - Holograph manuscript/typescript notes (Box-folder 5/8)
    - Lincoln: the great commoner (chorus, orchestra), undated, Poem by Edwin Markham.
      - Printed scores (Box-folder 5/7)
    - A set of pieces: for theatre or chamber orchestra, 1904-1911
      - Printed score (Box-folder 5/7)
    - Sonata no. 3 for piano and violin, 1951
      - Manuscript score paste-up (Box-folder 5/9)
      - Printed score (Box-folder 5/9)
    - Thirty-four songs (voice, piano), 1889-1921, Originally included in Ives' Book of 114 songs, G. Schirmer, Inc.
      - Holograph manuscript/printed scores, Selections only: No. 14, The Swimmers; No. 16, The rainbow; No. 24, Soliloquy, or, a study in 7ths and other things; No. 32, Song for harvest moon; No. 34, At parting (Box-folder 6/1-3)
      - Publisher's proofs (Box-folder 6/1-3)
    - Three protests (piano), 1947
      - Manuscript score paste-ups (Box-folder 3/3)
      - Printed score (Box-folder 3/3)
      - Correspondence (Box-folder 3/3)
  - Jackson, Howard
    - Blue flamingo: musical impression (piano), 1953
      - Printed score paste-up (Box-folder 6/4)
      - Printed score (Box-folder 6/4)
  - Jemnitz, Sándor
    - Second sonata for violin alone, op. 37, 1940
      - Printed score (Box-folder 6/5)
  - Kauder, Hugo
    - Quartet for oboe, clarinet, horn, and bassoon, 1948
      - Printed score (Box-folder 6/6)
  - Kaun, Bernhard
    - Quintet for oboe and strings, 1940
      - Printed score (Box-folder 6/7)
  - Kerr, Harrison
    - Notations on a sensitized plate: for voice, clarinet, string quartet, and piano, 1939, Poem by Cary Ross.
      - Photocopied holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 6/8)